quintura.com 2006-08-29

# Quintura - Privacy Policy

  |  | 

_Version 09/20/2005_

### Personal Information, Gathering

We will ask your permission to give away any information that we would need to personally identify you or contact you directly ("Personal Information"). Generally this is required when you subscribe to our newsletters or register your copies of our products.

  * When you subscribe to our newsletter or information letter about product updates, you are asked for your name and e-mail address.
  * We will use your IP address to help identify you and your navigation history on our site. This helps us see which parts of our site the users are visiting. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means, for instance, that a user's session will be tracked, but the user will remain anonymous. We do not use it for any other purposes.

When you submit personal information, it is kept in a secure database to ensure it is not used in any unauthorized data usage.

### Personal Information, Use of

Quintura, Inc. may share non-personal, summary information regarding its customers with partners or other third parties. However, any individual customer information provided for partners or third parties under contract with Quintura, Inc. shall be used only to perform or complete a necessary transaction or function related to the customer's purchase. These transactions or functions shall be in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy Statement. Quintura, Inc. will not share any individual customer information outside of the contracted partners and third parties mentioned above, without first receiving the individual's prior written approval. In some cases, Quintura, Inc. may use a visitor's personal information to understand overall patterns for web site usage, to contact the user for clarification on inaccurate information, or to follow up on a customer service issue. Personal information may include name, address, telephone number, etc.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small piece of information that a web site stores on your computer. When you revisit the web site, your browser sends the information back to that site. A cookie does not contain any Personal Information. The use of cookies is not required to browse through our site but it does enable us to better serve you when you return to our site by recording how and when you use it. You can set your browser to refuse cookies, but if you do, you might not be able to take full advantage of our site.

* * *

To help us improve our privacy policy, please [give us](mailto:support@quintura.com) your feedback, comments and suggestions.
